allgirlarcade.com 2015-05-29

# SparkCityWorld.com - Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy was last updated on June **2014**.

This Privacy Policy is designed to provide transparency into our privacy practices and principles. We are dedicated to treating your personal information with care and respect. 

This Privacy Policy applies to our Sites (defined below) and to our Mobile Apps or Apps (defined below) provided by Fuel Industries, Inc. and its subsidiaries in the U.S. ( **collectively** , **"Fuel Industries"** , **"we"** , **"our"** , or **"us"** ). This Privacy Policy governs your use of our Sites and Apps, regardless of how you access or use them. By "Sites", we mean www.sparkcityworld.com, www.allgirlarcade.com, and any affiliated website on which this Privacy Policy is posted, and including all services, features, applications, content, and downloads that are offered and operated by us, and that are available through our websites. By "Mobile Apps" and "Apps", we mean our products and services that we make available via mobile telecommunication platforms and/or through social networking platforms or App stores, and on which this Privacy Policy is posted. Each time you access and/or use the Sites or Apps, you agree to be bound by and comply with all of the terms of this Privacy Policy. Therefore, do not use the Sites or Apps if you do not agree to all of the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

This Privacy Policy explains what personal information we collect about you when you use the Sites or Apps, how the information will be used, with whom we share your information, and how you can control the collection, use and sharing of your information or update your information. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information we collect by other means (including offline) or from other sources. 

Your use of the Sites and Apps are also governed by our [Terms of Use](http://www.allgirlarcade.com/termsofuse/) into which this Privacy Policy is incorporated by reference. 

**Notice to Parents and Legal Guardians**

Fuel Industries and this Privacy Policy adhere to the requirements of the U.S. Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 ("COPPA") and the guidelines of the Children's Advertising Review Unit ("CARU") of the Council of Better Business Bureaus, Inc. in our Sites, online services and Apps directed to children under 13. Wherever we refer to "children" or a "child" in this Privacy Policy, we mean children under 13. Whenever we refer to "kids," we mean generally users who are underage minors. 

Our Sites and Apps offer various services directed at kids and their families, and therefore may involve the collection of children’s personal information. Upon registration, we ask users to provide a username and password, age, and a parent’s email address. We will use a parent’s email address for the purpose of providing a user’s parent with notice of information relating to this Privacy Policy and to obtain consent where required; and we will not use the parent’s email address for marketing purposes, unless the parent has consented to receiving marketing information (such as newsletters) from us. 

Consent from a child’s parent or legal guardian is required for the collection, use and disclosure of personal information about a child, and we describe below how and when we will seek parental consent. We also explain below the type of information we collect, how we use and share the information we collect, and your ability to review, edit and delete personal information collected by us. In any instance that we collect personal information from a child, we will retain that information only so long as reasonably necessary to allow the child the ability to participate in an activity or to use our services offered through the Sites or Apps, and to ensure the security of our users and our services, or as required by law. In the event we discover we have collected information from a child in a manner inconsistent with COPPA, we will either delete the information or immediately seek the parent’s or legal guardian’s consent for that collection. Please also help us protect your children's privacy by instructing them never to provide personal information (like their full name, email address, home address, telephone number, etc.) without your permission. 

**Notice to Kids**

We strongly encourage all kids to get parental permission to access or use our Sites and Apps. If you are under 13, you are required to get your parent's or legal guardian's permission before giving out your contact information, like email address or phone number, or any other personal information, to us or to anyone else. 

### Table of Contents:

  * Children Under the Age of 13
  * Adults and Teens
  * What Information is Collected 
  * How is Information Collected?
  * How Do We Use Your Information?
  * Interactive Forums, E-mails and "Chats" with Friends 
  * Newsletters and Updates
  * Opt-Out
  * Ability to Review, Edit and Delete Personal Information
  * Data Retention
  * Security
  * Global Data Transfers, Storage and Processing
  * Special Information for California Residents
  * Amendments to Privacy Policy
  * Contact Us

### Children Under the Age of 13

We take many special precautions to protect the privacy of children under 13. Through our Sites and Apps intended for use by children, we do not collect personal information (like first and last name, email address, phone number or home address, and persistent identifiers such as an IP address) from children without verifiable consent of a parent or legal guardian, except in limited circumstances authorized by law. We also take steps to prevent children from posting or publicly disclosing personal contact information. 

When a child seeks to register with us through our Sites or Apps, we collect the following information: age, username, password and parent's email address (to be used for obtaining consent, as set forth above in the section "Notice to Parents and Legal Guardians"). 

In addition, we may ask all users to voluntarily provide personal information and we may collect other information (like IP address, mobile device UDID/device identifier, operating system, etc.) automatically and use technology like cookies to provide functionality and support our operations. Please refer to the section "What Information is Collected?" below for a further explanation of the type of information we collect from all users, including children. In instances where we collect information from a child, we do not ask for more personal information than is necessary for a child to participate in an activity. 

**Verifiable Parental Consent**

In circumstances where we seek parental consent, we will send an email to the parent or legal guardian of a child to and provide the applicable parent or legal guardian with a "Direct Notice" as required under COPPA, notifying the type of personal information that may be collected from the child and how such information may be used and/or disclosed by us, and obtain verifiable consent from the parent or legal guardian. The Direct Notice will provide directions that the parent is required to follow in order to provide us with consent to the collection, use and/or disclosure of the child’s personal information, and instructions on how the parent can revoke such consent. 

Specifically, Direct Notice to the parent or legal guardian will contain a link to this Privacy Policy and explain the following: (i) that we have obtained the parent’s email address in order to obtain the parent’s consent; (ii) the purposes for which we are seeking to collect personal information from the parent’s child; (iii) that the parent’s consent is required for the child’s use of our Sites or Apps, and that we will not collect, use or disclose any personal information from the child if the parent does not provide such consent; (iv) the potential items of personal information we intend to collect from the child if the parent provides consent; (v) how the parent can provide verifiable consent to collection, use, and disclosure of the child’s personal information; and (vi) that we will delete the parent’s email address from our records if the parent does not provide consent within a reasonable time from the date the notice was sent. 

A parent or legal guardian may consent to our use of a child’s personal information without also consenting to the disclosure of the child’s personal information to third parties other than our Service Providers. You may contact us at _[customersupport@fuelindustries.com](mailto:customersupport@fuelindustries.com)_ to request that we do not disclose the use of your child’s personal information to these third parties, or to update or delete your child’s information. 

In the event that we change our policy with respect to the collection of personal information from children, or if new features, contests or sweepstakes which a child wishes to use or participate in require the provision of personal information, their parent or guardian will be notified and will be required to give their consent to the collection and use of this information and/or be given the option to opt out of participation. 

Back to Top

### Adults and Teens

We may collect information from adults and teens to serve your needs, manage our content and advertising, operate efficiently, and improve our products and services. 

We collect personal contact information, like e-mail address or phone number, from consumers 13 or older when voluntarily submitted, including when needed to fulfill transactions. Registration may be required to use some Sites, services or Apps. 

We may obtain information from commercial sources and combine it with information we have collected. 

Certain information may be collected automatically at our Sites or Apps, like your IP address, UDID/device identifier, browser setting, operating system, referring domain, language preferences, mobile carrier if you are using a mobile device, general location (e.g., zip code, but not specific address without consent) and other information. 

Third parties may also collect certain information via our Sites or Apps. 

Back to Top

### What Information is Collected

We collect two basic types of information - personal information and anonymous information - and we may use personal and anonymous information to create a third type of information, aggregate information. We collect the following categories of information from all users: 

  * Information you provide when you create an account, including your first name and surname, country of residence, gender, date of birth, email address, username and password. We also collect a parent’s email address but do not collect the child’s own email address. Users may also have the opportunity to upload a profile picture or personal video. 
  * Transaction information you provide when you request information or purchase a product or service from us, whether on our Sites or through our Apps, including your postal address, telephone number and payment information. However, we do not store credit card or debit card account numbers or other billing information, which are stored by our third party payment partners, including iTunes and Playspam, and we encourage you to visit their websites and review their privacy policies.
  * Information you provide in public forums on our Sites or Apps.
  * Information and communications sent either one-to-one or within a limited group using our message, chat, post or similar functionality, where we are permitted by law to collect this information.
  * Information you provide to us when you use our Sites or Apps, our applications on third-party sites or platforms such as social networking sites, or link your profile on a third-party site or platform with your registration account.
  * Location information when you visit our Sites or use our Apps, including location information either provided by a mobile device (such as geolocation data) interacting with one of our Sites or Apps, or associated with your IP address, where we are permitted by law to process this information. We will not collect geolocation data or any other location information from children without first obtaining verifiable parental consent.
  * Usage, viewing and technical data when you open emails we send, visit our Sites, and use our online services and Apps including on third-party sites or platforms. We also collect persistent identifiers such as unique device identifiers (UIDs), cookies that identify your computer or network, and IP address.

Back to Top

### How is Information Collected?

We collect information about you that you provide voluntarily (such as by registering and creating an account with us, or by communicating with us through any means), and information that is automatically collected through the use of tracking mechanisms and other technology. We may also acquire information from third party sources to update or supplement the information you provided or we collected automatically. You may be required to authorize the third party to share your information with us before we can acquire it. 

**Cookies and Technology**

Cookies and web beacons: Our Sites and Apps use technology, such as cookies, Flash cookies (also known as local shared objects), and web beacons that track information about you, including when you visit our Sites and Apps or use our applications on third-party websites or platforms, to manage registrations or access to certain features, store your settings and preferences, conduct age-screening, offer you personalized content, shop, help us understand the features that appeal to visitors, and manage advertising, among other things. 

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies but visitors always have the option of disabling cookies and you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you refuse cookies, you may be limited in your ability to access and/or use our services, content, and features. 

The use of cookies and web beacons by third parties is not covered by this Privacy Policy. We do not have access or control over tracking technologies used by third parties. 

Do Not Track Signals and Similar Mechanisms: Certain web browsers enable users to transmit "do-not-track" signals to websites. We adhere to the standards set out in this Privacy Policy but we do not take any specific action in response to these signals. We may reassess how we respond to these signals as industry standards evolve. 

**IP Addresses and Other Data**

Our Sites recognize information about your computer, such as the browser, operating system, IP address, and the home server from which you access the Internet. Your IP address is used to help gather broad demographic data, identify trends and statistics, help diagnose problems with our server, and administer our website. We may use your IP address information when compiling and reporting aggregate information about our website such as the number of visits to different pages on our site. We use the aggregate information to improve access to our content. 

**App Controls**

With Apps, your device may allow you to block or manage push notifications, location information, manage or restrict in-app purchases, or ability to access the web by turning off network access or turning off the browser. Access to or availability of controls may vary depending on your device. 

Apps that are directed at children will not use push notifications unless verifiable parental consent is obtained. 

**Third Party Tracking and Analytics**

Our Sites and Apps may link to third party websites, whose privacy and data collection practices may differ from ours. We also work with third parties who offer analytics or deliver targeted ads through our Sites and Apps. These third party websites, advertisers, or companies working on their behalf may use cookies, web beacons and other tracking mechanisms to collect certain information about you and/or your computer network (such as your IP address, mobile UDID or other device identifier, and information about your activities) over time and across different websites, to provide targeted or personalized content or advertising (also referred to sometimes as online behavioral advertising or interest-based advertising). We do not have access or control over the tracking mechanisms used by these third parties. You are encouraged to review the privacy policies of the different websites you visit. 

Our partners include Tapjoy, Inc. (http://home.tapjoy.com) and AdColony/Jirbo, Inc. (http://adcolony.com). For more information about the privacy practices of these companies, please visit their websites and review their policies or contact them directly. In addition, for information about how tracking works for online advertising purposes you can visit http://www.aboutads.info/choices. 

**Information Provided Through Your Use of Social Media**

The Sites and Apps may be designed to enhance user experience by providing ways to communicate with us and other users through various third party social media services, such as Facebook. By logging in to a third party social media service used to access or communicate on the Sites or Apps, you give us permission to access, store and use any information that you permit the applicable third party social media service to share with us in accordance with the privacy settings that apply to your account with the third party social media service, and to combine that information with other information we have collected about you. 

Back to Top

### How Do We Use Your Information?

We use the information we collect about you for the following purposes: 

  * To communicate with parents and legal guardians regarding their child's registration and to provide notice and information about their child’s account.
  * For marketing and promotional purposes, and to send you information regarding the products or services of third parties that you have opted to receive, however, we will not disclose your personal information to these third parties and you have the ability to opt out of receiving this information by following the unsubscribe instructions included in any promotional email.
  * To provide our services to you and to communicate with you about your use of our services, Sites and Apps.
  * To tailor the content and information that we may send or display to you, and to otherwise personalize your experiences while using the Sites and Apps.

**Sharing of Your Personal Information**

Except as explained in this Privacy Policy, we will not disclose your personal information without your prior consent. Personal information collected by us may be shared as follows: (a) within our family of companies; (b) with third party service providers, as described below, provided that such disclosure will be limited to information needed to deliver their service, and further provided that such third parties shall be prohibited from using the information for any other purpose; (c) with our third party marketing partners and advertisers to provide relevant advertising and marketing communications to you; (d) to conform to the law or comply with legal process served on us; (e) to protect and defend our rights and property (including the Sites and Apps), or personal safety of our users and third parties; and (f) we may disclose and transfer personal information as part of a sale or transfer of substantially all of its assets, or the assets related to a particular line of business, to a third party, whether by way of asset sale, merger, amalgamation, share purchase or any other form transaction, provided that such third party agrees to protect the personal information with no less a degree of care as set out within this policy. 

**Service Providers**

We use third parties to provide services for us such as a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services, providers who operate or support the Sites, Apps, and our network communications, and providers of other services that pertain to our internal operations. These third party service providers are prohibited from using or disclosing your personal information for promotional purposes or any other purpose unrelated to the service for which the provider was retained by us to perform. 

Our service providers include: 

Name of Third Party Partner | What info is shared with or collected by this partner | Partner’s purpose | Link to Partner’s privacy policy  
---|---|---|---  
[static.pbc.com](http://static.pbc.com/) (Playpsan) | None | Static Content (Images, CSS Styles) for Playspan lightbox | <http://www.playspan.com/privacy>  
Google Inc. (Analytics) | IP Address | Analytics | <http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html>  
[playspan.com](http://playspan.com/) | Billing Information (Address, Credit Card), Player ID | Membership Billing | <http://www.playspan.com/privacy>  
cdn.sparkcityworld.com | None | Static Content (Images, CSS, Flash content) for Spark City World | <http://www.sparkcityworld.com/privacypolicy/>  
  
If you have any inquiries regarding our partner’s privacy practices or how they use your child’s personal information, please contact us directly at _[customersupport@fuelindustries.com](mailto:customersupport@fuelindustries.com)_ .

**Third Party Marketing or Advertising Partners**

Our marketing partners include Tapjoy, Inc. (http://home.tapjoy.com) and AdColony/Jirbo, Inc. (http://adcolony.com). We share anonymous usage data but do not disclose personal identifying information of our users with our marketing partners. 

**User-Generated Content**

You may be able to post or upload content, like comments, reviews, photos, etc. Registration may be required. 

At Sites or Apps directed at children, parental consent is required and we may use filtering technology to prevent children from posting personal contact information without parental consent. 

Back to Top

### Interactive Forums, E-mails and "Chats" with Friends

We may provide users the opportunity to send games and other messages to family or friends. In order to send such messages, we ask users to submit the email address of the recipient. 

We also provide the opportunity to send communications to us through email and other means. We may ask for first names, but we request no personally identifiable information except an email address, which we use solely for the purpose of responding to messages and/or requests. 

All information collected for sending games and other messages and for responding to email messages is used only to send the requested game or email message and to respond to email questions and/or requests and is deleted from our system once the game, email message or email response is sent. 

Some of our Sites and Apps provide a messaging service or other interactive forums so that registered users participate in "chats" or other forms of dialogue with their friends. In some cases, chat messages can only include predetermined words and phrases, so that kids cannot send personal information. Users are prohibited from disclosing personal information including passwords, first and last names, phone numbers, email addresses, instant message screen names or other contact information when use the interactive forums or chat rooms on our Sites. IF A USER CHOOSES TO MAKE ANY OF HIS OR HER PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE OR OTHER INFORMATION PUBLICLY AVAILABLE IN AN INTERACTIVE FORUM OR CHAT ROOM, HE OR SHE DOES SO AT HIS OR HER OWN RISK. We do not allow children access to these messaging services or forums without parental consent and we strongly encourage parents to monitor their child's messages and online activities. 

Back to Top

### Newsletters and Updates

Users are able sign up for newsletters notifying them of offers, features, games, and services. The Direct Notice email has a link to sign up for the Newsletter. Signing up for the newsletter is not a requirement for registration. Parents may opt out of the newsletter at any time, simply contact us at _[customersupport@fuelindustries.com](mailto:customersupport@fuelindustries.com)_ and request to have your email removed from our newsletter list. 

Back to Top

### Opt-Out

We provide choices on how your personal information is used by us. If you do not wish your contact information to be used to receive our newsletter or any marketing or promotional information from us via email, you may simply opt out of receiving such information by following the unsubscribe instructions included in any promotional email, or contact us at _[customersupport@fuelindustries.com](mailto:customersupport@fuelindustries.com)_ . 

Back to Top

### Ability to Review, Edit and Delete Personal Information

Registered users (or parents or legal guardians of kids under 13 who are registered on the Site) can review, edit and/or request the deletion of personal information we have stored regarding them or their children by contacting _[customersupport@fuelindustries.com](mailto:customersupport@fuelindustries.com)_ . Upon request of a parent whose child has provided personal information to us, we will provide a description of the specific types or categories of personal information collected from the parent’s child. We may also request additional information in order to verify the parent’s identity if such a request is made (including, for example, by obtaining a signed form from the parent via postal mail or facsimile, accepting and verifying a credit card number, and by email accompanied by a digital signature or a PIN or password obtained through a verification method). 

Parents also have the right to refuse further collection and use of the child's personal information by contacting us at _[customersupport@fuelindustries.com](mailto:customersupport@fuelindustries.com)_ . 

Back to Top

### Data Retention

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

Back to Top

### Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can email us at _[customersupport@fuelindustries.com](mailto:customersupport@fuelindustries.com)_. 

Back to Top

### Global Data Transfers, Storage and Processing

We operate globally and may transfer your personal information to individual companies or third parties in locations around the world for the purposes described in this privacy policy. Wherever your personal information is transferred, stored or processed by us, we will take reasonable steps to safeguard the privacy of your personal information. Additionally, when using or disclosing personal information transferred from the European Union, we abide by the Safe Harbor Principles as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce, use standard contract clauses approved by the European Commission, adopt other means under European Union law for ensuring adequate safeguards, or obtain your consent. We also apply the substantive requirements of the Safe Harbor Principles when transferring personal information from Australia. 

Back to Top

### Special Information for California Residents

California residents may request and receive once a year, free of charge, a list of certain third parties to which we have disclosed personal information about you for their own direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year. If applicable, the notice will identify the categories of information shared, the names and addresses of the third parties with which information was shared. You may make one request per calendar year. In your request, please attest to the fact that you are a California resident and provide a current California address for your response. You may request this information in writing by contacting us at: _[customersupport@fuelindustries.com](mailto:customersupport@fuelindustries.com)_. Please allow up to thirty (30) days for a response. 

In addition, if you are a California resident under the age of 18 and are a registered user, you may request us to remove content or information posted on our Sites or stored on our servers by (a) submitting a request in writing to _[customersupport@fuelindustries.com](mailto:customersupport@fuelindustries.com)_ and (b) clearly identifying the content or information you wish to have removed and providing sufficient information to allow us to locate the content or information to be removed. However, please note that we are not required to erase or otherwise eliminate content or information if (i) other state or federal laws require us or a third party to maintain the content or information; (ii) the content or information was posed, stored, or republished by another user; (iii) the content or information is anonymized so that the minor cannot be individually identified; (iv) the minor does not follow the instructions posted in this Privacy Policy on how to request removal of such content or information; and (v) the minor has received compensation or other consideration for providing the content. Further, nothing in this provision shall be construed to limit the authority of a law enforcement agency to obtain such content or information. 

Users must delete any Apps installed on their devices in order to delete any information stored locally through use of our Apps. 

Back to Top

### Amendments to Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time by notifying you of the existence of a new privacy policy. If we make material changes to our privacy practices and this Privacy Policy, we will post notice of such changes to this policy on our Sites at least 30 days prior to their taking effect. If you have provided us with your email address, we will also send you a copy to the email address we have on file for you. It is therefore important that you keep the email address you provide to us current and to promptly notify us if your email address changes by contacting us at _[customersupport@fuelindustries.com](mailto:customersupport@fuelindustries.com)_ so that you may receive any notices we send to you regarding material changes to this Privacy Policy. We also encourage you to periodically review this page to ensure that you are familiar with the most current version of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with any changes made to this Privacy Policy, you must discontinue your use of our website before it takes effect. Your continued use of the applicable website after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgement of the modified privacy policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by the modified privacy policy. 

If we make material changes to how we use personal information collected from children under age 13, we will notify parents by email in order to obtain verifiable parental consent for the new uses of the child's personal information 30 days prior to the change becoming effective. 

Back to Top

### Contact Us

If you have any questions concerning this Privacy Policy, you may contact us at:

**SparkCityWorld.com**  
**c/o Fuel Industries**  
**7 Hinton Ave., North**  
**Suite 100**  
**Ottawa, ON Canada K1Y 4P1**  
**Email address:** [support@SparkCityWorld.com](mailto:support@SparkCityWorld.com)  
**Telephone:** 1.877.903-3835  

Back to Top
